[{"answer": "Right from the start we didn't do it right. Could you kneel down", "docId": "Moonstruck.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Yes, on the floor", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Where? At the City Hall? No! I want the whole wedding or we will have Bad Luck. For a whole wedding to be planned, a date must be set", "docId": "Moonstruck.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "A month from today", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "I have put a curse on that plane. My sister is on that plane. I have put a curse on that plane that it should explode. Burn on fire and fall into the sea. Fifty years ago she stole a man from me. Today she told me that she didn't even love him. She took him to feel strong with me. Now she goes back to that place. I have cursed her that the green that place water should swallow her up", "docId": "Moonstruck.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": " Neither do I", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "I won't come", "docId": "Moonstruck.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "I didn't give you away the first time", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Don't fight", "docId": "Moonstruck.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "He should pay", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Why", "docId": "Moonstruck.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "You are going to marry my brother", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "No, I want you to see this! I want you to watch me kill myself so you can tell my brother on his wedding day! my friend, gimme the big knife", "docId": "Moonstruck.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": " Do you know about me", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Where'd my friend find you", "docId": "Moonstruck.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "How'd he die", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Me neither", "docId": "Moonstruck.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "I was dead, too", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "I want to cut you open and crawl inside of you. I want you to swallow me", "docId": "Moonstruck.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Get all of me. Take everything", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "I never seen anybody so in love like that place back then! He'd stand outside the house all day and look in the windows. I never told you this cause it's not really a story. But one time I woke up in the middle of the night cause this bright light was in my face. Like a flashlight. I couldn't think a what it was. I looked out the window, and it was the moon! Big as a house! I never seen the moon so big before or since. I was almost scared, like it was gonna crush the house. And I looked down, and standing there in the street was that place, looking up at the windows. This is the funny part. I got mad at you, that place! I thought you brought this big moon over to my house cause you were so in love and woke me up with it. I was half asleep I guess and didn't know no better", "docId": "Moonstruck.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "No. You were there", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Oh", "docId": "Moonstruck.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "What are you talking about, my friend? that place can't own the moon", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "It's that place's moon", "docId": "Moonstruck.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "I mean it's that moon I was talking about at dinner.  Is he down there? No", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "What are you talking about, my friend? that place can't own the moon", "docId": "Moonstruck.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Is who down there", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "She didn't like me", "docId": "Moonstruck.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "What did you do", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "You don't get along with anybody", "docId": "Moonstruck.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "What did I do", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "Alright", "docId": "Moonstruck.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "Alright. Where's the Met", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "that place's cheating on me", "docId": "Moonstruck.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "A wife knows", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "I'm a professor. I teach communications at N.Y.U", "docId": "Moonstruck.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "my friend? Yes she was. Is. Was", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "Yes", "docId": "Moonstruck.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": " I'll remember that. What do you do", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "I got it done", "docId": "Moonstruck.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "What are you doing here", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "You're my father", "docId": "Moonstruck.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "I don't know whether I saw you or not", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "Yes", "docId": "Moonstruck.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "It's a house", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "We could go to my apartment. You could see how the other half lives", "docId": "Moonstruck.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "I'm too old for me. That's my predicament", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": "Why", "docId": "Moonstruck.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": "I was", "qsentId": 50}, {"answer": "Moving in", "docId": "Moonstruck.txt", "asentId": 53, "question": "Come on in", "qsentId": 52}, {"answer": "Well. I don't really know where to start", "docId": "Moonstruck.txt", "asentId": 55, "question": "Everything's different", "qsentId": 54}, {"answer": "Everything's different", "docId": "Moonstruck.txt", "asentId": 57, "question": "No. Are you drunk", "qsentId": 56}, {"answer": "She recovered", "docId": "Moonstruck.txt", "asentId": 59, "question": "It was a miracle", "qsentId": 58}, {"answer": "WHAT!! She was dying", "docId": "Moonstruck.txt", "asentId": 61, "question": "A miracle? This is modern times! There ain't supposed to be miracles any more", "qsentId": 60}, {"answer": "And go to confession", "docId": "Moonstruck.txt", "asentId": 63, "question": "Your life is not built on nothing. Ti amo", "qsentId": 62}, {"answer": "Have you come to make peace with me", "docId": "Moonstruck.txt", "asentId": 65, "question": "Of course I want to", "qsentId": 64}, {"answer": "It was a miracle", "docId": "Moonstruck.txt", "asentId": 67, "question": "I have something to tell you. But I must talk to you alone", "qsentId": 66}, {"answer": "my friend, I have something to tell you", "docId": "Moonstruck.txt", "asentId": 69, "question": "I have no secrets from my family", "qsentId": 68}, {"answer": "What the hell are you talking about? We're engaged", "docId": "Moonstruck.txt", "asentId": 71, "question": "I'm talking about a promise. You proposed to me", "qsentId": 70}]